<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!DOCTYPE resources [<!ENTITY appname "PocketCare S">]>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">&appname;</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Location</string>
    <string name="health_summary">Health</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Settings</string>
    <string name="contact"><p>Contact us: <a href="cse-pocketcares@buffalo.edu">cse-pocketcares@buffalo.edu</a></p></string>
    <string name="about"><![CDATA[
		<p>PocketCare S uses Bluetooth to enable smartphones to send and receive beacon signals. It checks the distance between a smartphone and another beacon (or
		 smartphone running the same app) to see if they are within 2 meters from each other, and if so, the smartphone records the duration of such a close
		 encounter with another beacon.

        <p>It provides each user with social distance information such as the number of other users
		who have been in close proximity with the user on a hourly and daily basis. It also
		reports to the user the duration of the close encounter sessions the user was involved,
		and alerts the user if the duration of the current session exceeds a certain threshold.</p>

		<p>For administrators of an organization (whose members adopt PocketCare S), social distance
		information aggregated over all of its member users such as the total number and duration of
		close encounters in the workplace will be made available through an analytics dashboard, which
		responds to queries such as “what is the number (or the percentage) of the users who have had
		more (or less) than “x” number (or minutes) of close encounters?”.  Such information will
		empower both users and employers to practice and encourage good social distancing in the workplace.</p>

		<p>PocketCare S is built upon a previous application, called PocketCare,
		developed five years ago by University at Buffalo (UB) faculty and students track the
		flu/virus propagation, and used by many volunteers. The new PocketCare
		S is the second generation of PocketCare, where “S” also stands for “Social distance”.</p>

        <p>For more information visit PocketCare S <a href="https://engineering.buffalo.edu/computer-science-engineering/pocketcares.html">website</a>.</p>
        ]]></string>
    <string name="privacy">
		<![CDATA[
		<p><h3><font color="#FFFFFF"><b>Data Collection and Privacy Policy</b></font></h3></p>

		<p>The App does not collect any specific information about you. In other words, all the data
		collected is anonymous and will not reveal any private personal information.</p>

		<p>The app collects anonymous ids of the beacons encountered, and estimates the
		duration of each close encounter session. Each smartphone randomly generates and
		frequently changes its anonymous id to be advertised to other smartphones to further
		protect privacy. Although the app requires the GPS to be turned on in order to
		determine if a close encounter with another beacon occurs on a campus or not, no GPS
		information is collected. Users are encouraged,<b> but are not required</b>, to provide a
		daily, anonymous health monitoring report, and other anonymous profile information
		such as age groups, zip code, gender and ethnicity. </p>

		<p> Some anonymized data collected will be stored in a secure server. Based on the
		anonymous data, the server will aggregate the information on the number and duration
		of close encounters on campus from all users, and make such aggregated information
		(instead of information about any particular individual) available to the public. </p>

		PocketCare S strictly adheres to the privacy policies reviewed and
        approved by <a href="https://www.research.buffalo.edu/rsp/irb/behavioral_sciences/">University at Buffalo Human Research Protection Program (IRB)</a>. More information about
        the data collection, usage, and Privacy Policy and FAQs can be found on our <a href="https://engineering.buffalo.edu/computer-science-engineering/pocketcares.html"> website </a>.
    	]]>
</string>

    <string name="usage_point_p1">
        <![CDATA[
		<p><h3><font color="#1E90FF"><b>Your Usage Point Status</b></font></h3></p>
    	]]>
    </string>

    <string name="usage_point_p2">
        <![CDATA[
        <p><h3><font color="#1E90FF"><b>What are usage points used for?</b></font></h3></p>
        <p>&#8226; Granting your levels to unlock features in the feature tab</p>
        <p>&#8226; Used as very important metric as the chance to win prizes in each raffle cycle</p>
        
		<p><h3><font color="#1E90FF"><b>How to earn usage points fast</b></font></h3></p>
		<p>You earn usage points by running the App with \"Scan service\" turned \"ON\" (this is a default setting) in \"Scan Settings\".  Points are calculated based on the number of \"scan\" reports generated by Bluetooth, GPS, WiFi and Activity Recognizer, so higher the frequency you set these interfaces to scan, the faster your points will likely to accumulate. You can also find the daily usage point earning rate based on your current configuration in the \"Scan service\" link.</p>
		<p>You also earn points by submitting daily health status report. While we encourage you to update your health status on the same day, you will not earn additional points by submitting health status more than once a day.</p>
    	]]>
    </string>

    <string name="feature_intro">
		<![CDATA[
        <p><h3><font color="#1E90FF"><b>Unlocking Features </b></font></h3></p>
		<p>PocketCare runs a background service to collect the proximity information and ultimately help model how epidemic diseases propagation through close proximity. In order to incentivize individual’s participation, the App is designed with several levels, each with a new feature, all of which help you discover interesting facts 
		on your daily behaviors and your smartphone usage. When you start the App at level one, only the basic feature is available (unlocked). However, as you keep the App running, you will accumulate more and more usage points, and when you reach the next level, a new feature will be unlocked. We plan to continue to develop new features (and please suggest us your suggestions) and release them in future versions of the App.</p> 
		<p><h3><font color="#1E90FF"><b>Features already unlocked</b></font></h3></p>
		<p>Following is a list of features that are already unlocked to you:</p>
    	]]>
    </string>

    <string name="feature_rank_title">Show your rank</string>
    <string name="feature_rank_detail">Show your rank of usage point among all other users in each promotion period, which is related to our awarding policy. Please check \"Prizes\" in setting tab for more details.</string>
    <string name="feature_yesterday_title">Show yesterday status</string>
    <string name="feature_yesterday_detail">Show a summary of your yesterday status, including the mileage you have covered, your health status, the number of unique Bluetooth device you have encountered(detected) and the number of unique WiFi access point you have seen</string>
    <string name="feature_symptomtip_title">Health tips</string>
    <string name="feature_symptomtip_detail">Based on the health status you reported, we give you some health tips and suggestions to help you recover from it :)</string>
    <string name="feature_btenctr_title">Bluetooth encounters</string>
    <string name="feature_btenctr_detail">Among all the Bluetooth devices you have detected, how many of them are installed with the same application?</string>
    <string name="feature_btnotify_title">BT encounter notification</string>
    <string name="feature_btnotify_detail">Notify the presence of bluetooth dTestevice of your interest if it is in your vicinity. You can designate a bluetooth device and choose time interval between two consective notifications</string>
    <string name="feature_plot_health_title">Plot health status</string>
    <string name="feature_plot_health_detail">Plot a graph showing your historical health status. The health score on a scale from 0 to 5 based on your daily health report, 5 for feeling good and for each symptom the score is decreased by 1. If you dont submit health report, health score is 0.</string>
    <string name="feature_plot_bt_title">Plot Bluetooth encounters</string>
    <string name="feature_plot_bt_detail">Plot a graph showing a record of your encounters with Bluetooth devices in general, which means any devices with a bluetooth interface(headset, laptop or the ones installed with the same application)</string>
    <string name="feature_plot_mile_title">Plot mileage</string>
    <string name="feature_plot_mile_detail">Plot a graph showing the distance you have covered every day</string>
    <string name="feature_wifi_summary">Show summary of WiFi APs</string>
    <string name="feature_wifi_summary_detail">Display a summary of the discovered WiFi Access Points, in a decreasing order of their frequencies</string>
    <string name="feature_plot_wifi_title">Plot WiFi access point</string>
    <string name="feature_plot_wifi_detail">Plot the number of distinct WiFi access point discovered every day</string>
    <string name="feature_plot_act_title">Plot activities</string>
    <string name="feature_plot_act_detail">Plot a graph showing historical activity status</string>
    <string name="feature_recover_title">Recover summary</string>
    <string name="feature_recover_detail">Show you a summary of your recovery status based on the health report you submitted</string>
    <string name="feature_bench_title">Usage history</string>
    <string name="feature_bench_detail">Show aggregate information of your usage history, including the total number of distinct Bluetooth device you have detected, 
        the total number of unique WiFi access point you have discovered, the total number of health report you have submitted and the total mileaged you have travelled</string>
    <string name="feature_record_title">Personal record for the most</string>
    <string name="feature_record_detail">Show your own record for the most, including the Bluetooth device and WiFi access point that you have seen for the most times, 
        the longest recover time based on your health report and the longest distance you have travelled in a single day</string>
    <string name="feature_alert_title">Epidemic alert</string>
    <string name="feature_alert_detail">Give you information based on health reports from users and users your have encountered</string>
    <string name="feature_download_title">Download</string>
    <string name="feature_download_detail">Download your own data locally to this device</string>

    <string name="feature_no_next_title">Out of Feature</string>
    <string name="feature_no_next_detail">There are no more available features at next level from now on :(</string>
    <string name="feature_locked_prompt"><![CDATA[This feature is locked at now, upgrade to next level will unlock it! You can find more details about gaining levels and usage points in \"Usage Points\" at setting tab]]></string>

    <string name="feature_btnotify_selectbt">Select one from the following detected bluetooth devices so that PocketCare will notify you when it is around</string>
    <string name="feature_btnotify_selectinterval">Select the time interval between two consective notification when designated BT mac is detected</string>
    <string name="feature_wfsummary_title">Following is a list of WiFi Access Points you have discovered sorted based on their frequencies</string>

    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_generalinfo">General Info</string>
    <string name="menu_reporthealth">Report Health</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About</string>
    <string name="surveystr_gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="surveystr_age">Age</string>
    <string name="surveystr_occupation">Occupation</string>
    <string name="surveystr_encounter">Encounters</string>
    <string name="surveystr_gender_male">Male</string>
    <string name="surveystr_gender_female">Female</string>

    <string name="percent_sign">&#x0025;</string>

    <string-array name="op530_human">
        <item>every 15 minutes</item>
        <item>every 30 minutes</item>
        <item>every 60 minutes</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="op530_values">
        <item>15</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>60</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="op1060_human">
        <item>every 10 minutes</item>
        <item>every 15 minutes</item>
        <item>every 30 minutes</item>
        <item>every 60 minutes</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="op1060_values">
        <item>10</item>
        <item>15</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>60</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="setting_fq_default_bluetooth">15</string>
    <string name="setting_fq_default_wifi">15</string>
    <string name="setting_fq_default_gps">30</string>
    <string name="setting_fq_default_activityrecognition">15</string>
    <string name="setting_bt_list_summary">Bluetooth will scan</string>
    <string name="setting_wf_list_summary">WiFi will scan</string>
    <string name="setting_gps_list_summary">GPS will scan</string>
    <string name="setting_ac_list_summary">Activity Recognizer will scan</string>
    <string name="content_description">Content Description</string>
    <string name="enter_refer_id">Enter Refer ID</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>

    <string name="no_network">Unable to connect to internet</string>
    <string name="action_retry">Retry connection</string>
    <string name="update_application">Application is out of date.</string>
    <string name="action_update">Update</string>


    <string-array name="gen_op_gender">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gen_op_age">
        <item>18~24</item>
        <item>25~64</item>
        <item>above 65</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gen_op_ub">
        <item>yes</item>
        <item>no</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gen_op_occupation">
        <item>CSE Grad</item>
        <item>CSE Under</item>
        <item>CSE Staff/faculty</item>
        <item>All Others</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gen_op_course">
        <item>0~4</item>
        <item>5~9</item>
        <item>above 10</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gen_op_contact">
        <item>0~4</item>
        <item>5~9</item>
        <item>above 10</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gen_cache_upload">
        <item>3</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>14</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list1">
        <item>Item 1</item>
        <item>Item 2</item>
        <item>Item 3</item>
        <item>Item 4</item>
        <item>Item 5</item>
        <item>Item 6</item>
        <item>Item 7</item>
        <item>Item 8</item>
        <item>Item 9</item>
        <item>Item 10</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="list2">
        <item>Item 1</item>
        <item>Item 2</item>
        <item>Item 3</item>
        <item>Item 4</item>
        <item>Item 5</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="LevelOfUser">5</string>

    <string name="health_data_spinner_prompt">Select range</string>
    <string-array name="health_data_spinner">
        <item>Past 7 days</item>
        <item>Past 14 days</item>
        <item>Past 21 days</item>
        <item>Past 30 days</item>
        <!-- <item>Past all days</item> -->
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="health_report_group">
        <item>I am feeling fine</item>
        <item>I have the following symptoms:\n(check all that apply)</item>
        <item>My roommate is sick</item>
        <item>Someone I met today was sick</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="ret">Return</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>

    <string-array name="fever_tips">
        <item>Fever. A fever is a part of the body\'s defense against infection. Although a fever is not an illness, if it exceeds temperatures of 40C (104F), it can become very dangerous. However, for most fevers, there is no option but to ride it out at home.</item>
        <item>Take a bath. If you want some relief and a treatment for your fever, go relax in a tub full of cool water. The water will help to cool the skin and will evaporate as you soak, cooling you further.</item>
        <item>Sponge down. If a bath doesn\'t sound too appealing, use a moist towel instead. Soak small towels in cool water and dab them over your body. Again, you will benefit from the further cooling by evaporation. Leave a cloth on your forehead to soothe any discomfort caused by the fever.</item>
        <item>Lower the room temperature. Reduce the temperature of your home to help keep cool. Lowering the room temperature will likely feel more comfortable and will also help to reduce the temperature of your body. The fan will provide additional cooling and relief.</item>
        <item>Remove layers of clothing. Bundling under layers of clothing and blankets traps heat, making a fever last longer than usual. Wear only a 1 layers of clothing and only use a blanket for periods of chills. If in bed, use only a sheet and get rid of the blanket or comforter.</item>
        <item>Get lots of rest. Your body is fighting against a sickness and needs plenty of energy to heal itself. Help provide this by limiting activity and resting or sleeping as much as possible. Avoid moving around much and if necessary, take time off of work.</item>
        <item>Try an all liquid diet. Nutrients in some foods can feed the bacteria that are causing your illness and the accompanying fever. So, it is best to starve out your sickness by fasting while you have the fever. On the other hand, the antioxidants packed into fruit seem to reduce fevers also. Therefore, fast while the fever persists or flood your body with the anti-oxidants found in most fruits. Both approaches have been shown to reduce the severity of a fever.</item>
        <item>Stay hydrated. Along with rest, your body needs plenty of liquids to fight the illness in your body, especially if you are fasting. Drink water frequently throughout the day, supplementing with clear broth and juice, if desired.</item>
        <item>Stay indoors. Unless you\'re already outdoors when your fever comes on, it is best to curl up and rest indoors where the air is dry and the temperature won\'t change much. If you must be outdoors while suffering from your fever, stay in the shade and limit activity.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="runnynose_tips">
        <item>Apply pressure. Press down 10 times on the corner of your nose, pressure very gently to keep your nose from getting worse. It is believed that this pressure point can help alleviate sinus congestion and headaches that result from colds and allergies. Your nose should be almost closed each time you apply pressure to the area. Repeat on the area just above your eyes, applying mild pressure. Repeat 10 times on each side of your face.</item>
        <item>Massage. Massage your earlobe for 10 seconds. Repeat on both sides.</item>
        <item>Irrigate. Use salt water to flush out the nasal passages, freeing up mucus and other debris. You can either use a syringe, neti pot, or other product designed for nasal irrigation. Alternatively, you can gently flush out your nose using water alone, but be sure that the water has either been filtered or previously boiled to make sure it is clean. Be careful not to inhale the water.</item>
        <item>Blow your nose. Runny noses result when you have excess mucus and fluid buildup in your nose and throat. The best way to treat a runny nose is to get the excess fluid out. Blow your nose gently, using a soft tissue to avoid skin irritation. Don\'t blow too often, as it could cause skin burning and redness.</item>
        <item>Apply a warm compress. Soak a hand towel in hot water and place it on your face. This will help alleviate sinus pressure and open up the nasal passages.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="coughing_tips">
        <item>Drink herbal tea with honey. Get into the habit of having a mug of non-caffeinated tea before bed. \"Any warm liquid can help break up mucus in your airways,\" says Norman H. Edelman, MD, chief medical officer of the American Lung Association. Add a little honey. </item>
        <item>Sleep on an incline. When it comes to nighttime cough, gravity is your enemy. All the postnasal drainage and mucus you swallow during the day backs up and irritates your throat when you lay down at night. Try to defy gravity by propping yourself up on some pillows while you sleep.</item>
        <item>Use steam cautiously. Dry airways can make your cough worse. You may find relief from taking a shower or bath before bed—or just sitting in a steamy bathroom. Edelman has one caution: \"If you have asthma, steam can actually make a cough worse.\"</item>
        <item>Prepare your bedside. In case you start coughing in the night, have everything you need by your bed—a glass of water, cough medicine or drops, and anything else that seems to help. The sooner you can stop a coughing fit, the better. Continually coughing irritates your airways, which can make your nighttime problem last longer.</item>
        <item>Keep bedding clean. If you have a cough and are prone to allergies, focus on your bed. Dust mites—tiny creatures that eat dead flakes of skin and lurk in bedding—are a common allergy trigger. To get rid of them, each week wash all your bedding in hot water, Edelman says. You may also want to wrap your mattress and pillows in plastic, as that can keep dust mites from invading.</item>
        <item>Consider medicine. Over-the-counter cough medicines can help in two ways. An expectorant can help loosen mucus. A cough suppressant blocks the cough reflex and reduces the urge to cough. Look carefully at the label to make sure you get the medicine that\'s right for your cough. Ask your pharmacist or doctor if you\'re not sure.</item>
        <item>See your doctor. If you\'ve had a nighttime cough for longer than 7 days, it\'s time to check in with your doctor. It may take some time, but together, you and your doctor can figure out the cause—and make your nights peaceful again.</item>
        <item>Watch the humidity. Humidifiers can help coughs if the air is dry. But too much moisture in your bedroom can keep you coughing, too. Dust mites and mold (both common allergens) thrive in damp air. It is suggested that you keep humidity levels at 40\u0025 to 50\u0025. To measure humidity, pick up an inexpensive device, such as a hygrometer at your hardware store.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sore_tips">
        <item>Water. Gargle with warm salt water to help reduce swelling and relieve discomfort: Gargle at least once each hour with 1 tsp (5 g) of salt dissolved in 8 fl oz (240 mL) of warm water. If you have postnasal drip, gargle often to prevent more throat irritation.</item>
        <item>Prevent dehydration. Fluids may help thin secretions and soothe an irritated throat. Hot fluids, such as tea or soup, may help decrease throat irritation.</item>
        <item>Use a vaporizer or humidifier in your bedroom. Warm or cool mist may help you feel more comfortable by soothing the swollen air passages. It may also relieve hoarseness. But don\'t let your room become uncomfortably cold or very damp. Use a shallow pan of water to provide moisture in the air through evaporation if you don\'t have a humidifier. Place the pan in a safe location where no one will trip on it or fall into it.</item>
        <item>Use nonprescription throat lozenges. Medicated throat lozenges or sprays have medicine (local anesthetic) that numbs the throat to soothe pain. Hard candy may also help. Think about buying the sugar-free kind.</item>
        <item>Use a decongestant or a steroid nasal spray. if you have a stuffy nose (congestion). These medicines make breathing easier by shrinking swollen mucous membranes in the nose, allowing air to pass through. They also help relieve a runny nose and postnasal drip, which can cause a sore throat. These medicines may not be safe for young children or for people who have certain health problems. Before you use them, check the label. If you do use these medicines, always follow the directions about how much to use based on age and in some cases weight. </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="nausea_tips">
        <item>Use acupressure. You can do this by applying your thumb to your wrist and pressing for 30 seconds. Your index and middle fingers should be on the top of your wrist.</item>
        <item>Fresh air. Get the air flowing. Have a fan blow on your face or body. This will reduce nausea, and will feel quite good. Get away from bad odors. Avoid sitting in hot rooms and avoid repulsive smells—which, when you\'re nauseous, is just about any smell at all.</item>
        <item>Non-prescription drugs. Seek relief with non-prescription drugs. Some over-the-counter medications such as Pepto-Bismol, Maalox and Mylanta help calm nauseated stomachs. Others include Emetrol and Nauzene. It depends on the cause of nausea, but an irritated stomach may feel better after a couple of spoonfuls. Anti-motion sickness drugs like Dramamine can also help as well. Some medications can cause nausea as a side effect. Talk to your doctor. Domperidone (sold as Motilium in the UK) works for some people.</item>
        <item>Foods that help ease nausea. Eat fiber rich foods. These remove nausea-inducing chemicals from your system. Have an apple or snack on raw vegetables; Snack on peanuts. Nuts and other protein rich foods replenish depleted energy and keep nausea at bay; Eat a banana. Bananas contain potassium that is lost during nauseous symptoms; Have some applesauce. Eat no more than a spoonful or so at a time, until your nausea has abated; Use ginger. Nibble crystallized ginger. Or, make ginger tea by grating fresh ginger, pour boiling water over it, allow to brew, then strain.</item>
        <item>Getting your mind off the nausea. Do something fun. Forget about the nausea. Watch a movie or talk to someone. Try playing a video game, listen to songs. Sometimes nausea is only in the mind. Try not to stress about being sick, anxiety can make nausea worse. Read a book, grab a crossword puzzle, or watch a movie!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="use_phone_tips">
        <item>Features will be gradually unlocked to you when you use our application. Unlocked features and next locked feature are displayed in the feature tab.</item>
        <item>Introduction of how to unlock features and gain levels can be found in \"Features\" in the setting tab</item>
        <item>Accepting our terms to run background service and submit your general information will directly upgrade you to level 1, granting the feature of showing your rank of usage points among all the users</item>
        <item>Set a higher scanning frequency will help you get usage points faster</item>
        <item>You can adjust interface scan frequency in \"Scan Setting\" from the setting tab</item>
        <item>Usage point is a measurement of how much you used our application, it is calculated based on the number of health report and number of interface scans</item>
        <item>Every two weeks, the user with the top 3 usage point of that cycle will be guaranteed to win a prize</item>
        <item>You can update your information anytime in \"User Information\" in the setting tab</item>
        <item>You can turn on tips all the time in \"Preference Setting\"</item>
        <item>Old local cache data can be configured when to be uploaded and deleted, check it up in \"Preference Setting\"</item>
        <item>Remember to report your health status every day correctly, this gives you a lot of usage points</item>
        <item>Check information in \"Prizes\" to learn more details about how we give away cool prizes</item>
        <item>Please like our facebook page "PocketCareUB", there is also a lot of useful information there</item>
        <item>Do not forget to check our notification dashboard item updated from server in the home tab frequently</item>
        <item>You can only earn usage points once from submitting health status every day</item>
        <item>You are free to turn on/off scan at night time, note that the scans will not be counted as usage point</item>
        <item>You can pull the list in home tab to update its content</item>
        <item>Turn off 2G/3G/LTE network data transmission to only allow data traffic through WiFi</item>
        <item>If the app stops working, please you hit the \"Report\" button to help us diagnose the problem, the scanning services will automatically resume in the background. You may also start the App manually if you want to access the features and menus etc.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="welcome_msg">Thank you for installing PocketCare. Please read the tips on how to earn points faster to unlock more and more features that will help you discover interesting facts about your smartphone usage and daily behaviors, as well as to enter bi-weekly raffles to win cool prizes during our promotion period. Take care and have fun!</string>

    <string name="download_description">Please select which month of data that you want to download from:</string>

    <string name="feature_unlocked">Features Unlocked</string>
    <string name="next_feature">Next Feature</string>

    <string name="setting_bt_summary">Scanning from bluetooth is binded to proximity service</string>

    <string name="warning_not_accetp_terms">You have not accepted our terms yet, you can accept it in \"About App\" of setting tab</string>
    <string name="warning_not_submit_general">You have not submitted your general information yet, check \"User Information\" in setting tab</string>
    <string name="warning_to_submit_general">You have not submitted your general information yet, click OK to submit it now or you can submit it from \"User Information\" anytime in setting tab</string>
    <string name="warning_not_network_time"><![CDATA[Please enable network-provided time to make contact measurement more accurate and save battery! You can check it in Android system "Settings" -> "Date & Time" -> "Automatic date & time"]]></string>
    <string name="warning_not_submit_healthreport">You have not submitted your health report today, click OK to submit it.</string>
    <string name="warning_geninfo_missing_field">The answers to some of the questions are still empty, please return to fill them!</string>
    <string name="warning_geninfo_resubmit">Your have submitted general information before, are you sure that you want to update the old one?</string>
    <string name="warning_no_data_database">There is no information recorded in local database, please try again later!</string>

    <string name="setting_seekbar_prompt">Please use the slide bar below to select a number:</string>
    <string name="update_generalinfo_prompt">You can update your information in \"User information\" from the setting tab anytime you want in the future</string>

    <string name="setting_general_click_to_set">Click to set</string>

    <string name="title_activity_splash">Splash</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>

    <string name="title_activity_disabled">DisabledActivity</string>
    <string name="corona_symptom">Based on the symptoms you selected, you should contact a medical professional immediately!</string>
    <string name="corona_title">Immediate Action Required</string>
    <string name="response_feedback">Health Response Feedback</string>
    <string name="healthy">You reported no symptoms, let’s stay healthy and fit.</string>
    <string name="normal_symptoms"> Please stay at home and continue to watch your symptoms daily. For more information visit: CDC Website</string>
    <string name="roommate_sick">Tell your roommate to take precautions and maintain appropriate distance from your roommate.</string>
    <string name="random_sick">Sanitize your hands and make sure you clean everything after the interaction.</string>
    <string name="no_health_report">You do not have any health report yet. Please enter your daily health report, it only takes a few seconds.</string>
    <string name="monitor">Take a few seconds to record your health status everyday.</string>
    <string name="idea">Learn tips and guidelines from health professionals.</string>
    <string name="location">Keep track of social distance with other users.</string>
    <string name="clean_hands"><![CDATA[<b>Clean Your Hands Often</b><br><br>Wash your hands regularly with soap and water for at least 20 seconds. Avoid touching your eyes, nose, and mouth with unwashed hands.]]></string>
    <string name="distance"><![CDATA[<b>Practice Social Distancing</b><br><br>Avoid close contact with others, keep about 6 feet between yourself and others, stay at home as much as possible.]]></string>
    <string name="mask"><![CDATA[<b>Cover Your Nose and Mouth</b><br><br>When going out in public, make sure to wear a face cover.]]></string>
    <string name="sneeze"><![CDATA[<b>Cover Coughs and Sneezes</b><br><br>Always cover your mouth and nose with a tissue when you cough or sneeze, and throw the used tissues directly in the trash.]]></string>
    <string name="clean"><![CDATA[<b>Clean and Disinfect</b><br><br>Clean and disinfect the frequently touched objects daily. This includes tables, doorknobs, light switches, etc.]]></string>
    <string name="stay_home"><![CDATA[<b>Stay at Home</b><br><br>Stay in your apartment or residence hall room when you are sick. Avoid any unnecessary travel, and limit shopping trips to those needed for essential supplies.]]></string>
    <string name="monitor_health"><![CDATA[<b> Monitor your health</b><br><br>Be alert for symptoms. Watch for symptoms including fever, cough, shortness of breath. Monitor your symptoms daily using the health monitor in the app.]]></string>

    <string name="title_activity_disclaimer">DisclaimerActivity</string>
    <string name="activity_disclaimer_paragraph">
        <![CDATA[
        <body>
            <p>PocketCare S, in its current form, is primarily intended to measure social distance. It can assist but is not intended for automating contact tracing operations. <br><br>
            The daily health report in PocketCare S neither provides diagnostic services nor substitutes medical treatment. If you currently feel seriously ill, please seek medical help.  <br><br>
            Due to inherent limitations of the smartphone technology used, PocketCare S does not guarantee the information on the number, duration or distance of the close encounters is accurate.
            The actual values may be above or below the estimated values.<br>
            </p>
            </body>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="introduction_activity">To learn more about &appname;, visit FAQs.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_permission_warning">PermissionWarningActivity</string>
    <string name="permission_activity_paragraph">
        <![CDATA[
        <body>
        <p>The app generates a randomized Bluetooth name to hide your identity.<br> The app will automatically change your Bluetooth Name.<br>Thank you.</p><br>
        </body>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="health_report_button">Health Report Button</string>
    <string name="close_contacts">Close Encounters</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_user_profile">User_Profile</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string-array name="ethnic_group">
        <item>Hispanic or Latino</item>
        <item>White</item>
        <item>Black or African American</item>
        <item>Native Hawaiian or Other Pacific Islander</item>
        <item>Asian</item>
        <item>American Indian or Alaskan Native</item>
        <item>Two or More Races</item>
        <item>Decline to self-identify</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="age_groups">
        <item>Under 21</item>
        <item>21–35</item>
        <item>36–50</item>
        <item>50–65</item>
        <item>Over 65</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="risk_conditions">
        <item>Asthma</item>
        <item>Chronic Diseases</item>
        <item>Diabetes</item>
        <item>Immunocompromised</item>
        <item>Liver disease</item>
        <item>Hemoglobin Disorders</item>
        <item>Serious Heart Conditions</item>
        <item>Severe Obesity</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="university_affiliation">
        <item>Faculty</item>
        <item>Staff</item>
        <item>Graduate Student</item>
        <item>Undergraduate Student</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="anonymousDescription">To protect your privacy, cloaked locations are sent to the server instead of your real locations. You can view the cloaked locations that are sent to the server.</string>
    <string name="closeContactInfo">A period of at least 5 minutes during which you are within 2 meters from another is called a close encounter. You will be notified if a close encounter session exceeds 10 minutes. Your close encounters are recorded in a log on your device, with a slight lag for privacy protection purposes.
Please check back for updates.</string>
    <string name="switchText">Real Locations </string>
    <string name="disclaimer_check">By checking this box, I have read and understood the data collection, usage, and privacy policy as well as the disclaimer, and agree to hold the app developers and their employers harmless for any and all consequences of using the &appname;.</string>
    <string name="activity_recognition_permission">The app uses activity recognition only to conserve your phone\'s battery. Your activity will not be recorded.</string>
    <string name="location_permission">Your location information is safely stored only on your phone. Please always allow GPS use.</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_description">&appname; requires bluetooth to be turned on to measure social distance.</string>
    <string name="optional_user_info">Sharing the information below is optional but highly encouraged. </string>
    <string name="first_time_location_info">On this screen, you can see a list of locations you have visited. The red pins will give you the real information from GPS and the blue pins will give you the corresponding cloaked (masked) location information that will be uploaded to the server.</string>
    <string name="first_time_close_encounters">On this screen, you will see information on close encounters with other &appname;
        users. </string>
    <string name="first_time_health_report">On this screen, you will see all of your daily health reports. We encourage you to enter this information daily. It only takes a few seconds.</string>
    <string name="health_report">Take a few seconds to record health status daily.</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_off">&appname; needs bluetooth to be turned on.</string>
    <string name="location_off">&appname; needs location to be turned on.</string>
    <string name="notification_reminder_title">Social Distance Notification</string>
    <string name="notification_reminder_description">Your current contact duration has exceeded 10 minutes. Please mind your social distance.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">SettingsActivity</string>

    <!-- Preference Titles -->
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>
    <string name="snooze_options_summary">Choose if/how to snooze the Social Distance notifications</string>
    <string name="notification_header">Notifications</string>
    <string name="scanning_header">Close Encounter Scanning</string>
    <string name="snooze_none_label">None</string>
    <string name="snooze_hour_label">Snooze for an Hour</string>
    <string name="snooze_day_label">Snooze for a Day</string>
    <string name="snooze_none_value">default</string>
    <string name="snooze_hour_value">snoozeHour</string>
    <string name="snooze_day_value">snoozeDay</string>
</resources>